#### Contact

danikvod@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/daniel-vodenejev-29a74617b (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Programming
Front-End Development
SQL

# Daniel Vodenejev

Asparing Junior Sowftware Developer Estonia

### Summary

I have graduated from Tartu Vocational College with a specialization in junior software development, where I acquired skills in programming and software development. I am passionate about becoming a competent software developer. I am a motivated young software developer who has experience working in teams. I enjoy learning new technologies and all relevant references can be found in my additional information. For more information, please visit my portfolio at https://daniilvodenejev.ikt.khk.ee/, and you can also explore my final college project at https://explorerstudio.kristaleks.ee, with its corresponding GitHub repository available at https://github.com/ibra101408/booking\_vue.

## Experience

Inforegister
Internship Trainee
September 2022 - December 2022 (4 months)

#### AMZ TRADE OÜ

Sales Employee

May 2020 - October 2022 (2 years 6 months)

Customer communication, e-commerce management.

Klick Eesti AS Sales Employee February 2019 - July 2019 (6 months)

Töö klientidega, arvutiga(erinevad süsteemid ja programmid), kaupaga.

Subway
Sales Employee
September 2018 - February 2019 (6 months)

Klienditenindamine, toidu valmistamine, kassa süsteemi kauba siisastamine

Page 1 of 2

## Education

Tartu Rakenduslik Kolledž

Software Development · (September 2021 - February 2024)

Tallinna Tööstushariduskeskus

· (September 2018 - May 2020)